and now we move on to the next segment
and can we have that on the screen
please
best branch digitization implementation
and here comes the envelope
and the winner is
winner is
ICICI Bank congratulations to team ICICI
Bank
and accepting the award for ICICI Bank
we have Mr Sanjay yadav
Mr nishikant goswami and the entire team
congratulations
foreign
take this award on behalf of our team
but you know whatever we do in designing
product or Building Product we keep in
mind that you know customer is at the
center So yeah thank you thank you
everyone
yeah congratulations ladies and
gentlemen that was ICICI Bank